<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Muranga County Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="attraction_card_image_view_content_desc">ImageView displaying the attraction\'s image file</string>
    <string name="list_item_image_view_content_desc">Image of Attraction</string>
    <string name="list_item_right_arrow_image_content_desc">Right arrow image to move forward to the next activity</string>
    <string name="detail_image_cd">Image of Attraction</string>
    <string name="map">Show in Map</string>
    <!-- Category name for Schools -->
    <string name="category_schools">Schools</string>

    <!-- Category name for Malls -->
    <string name="category_malls">Mall</string>

    <!-- Category name for Hotels -->
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotel</string>

    <!-- Category name for Restaurants -->
    <string name="historical_sites">Historic sites</string>

    <string name="Blue_Post_Hotel_name">Blue Post Hotel</string>
    <string name="blue_post_hotel_desc">The hotel next to Chania Falls. Beautiful scenery.
        You will lose yourself in the sight and sound of the Chania Falls when you stay at this hotel.
        One of the Oldest hotels in Kenya that must be one of the most beautiful and spacious hotels around.  </string>
    <string name="blue_post_hotel_addr">Blue Post Hotel, Thika - Muranga Road, Thika</string>

    <string name="golden_palm_breeze_name">Golden Palm Breeze Hotel</string>
    <string name="golden_palm_breeze_desc">Golden Palm Breeze Hotel is located off Kenol in Muranga, Kenya. Free WiFi is available,
        All rooms are air-conditioned and fitted with en-suite bathroom, flat screen TVs and double beds.
        The on-site restaurant serves local and continental complimentary breakfast which can be enjoyed at the on-site restaurant.
        Guests can also enjoy meals outdoors at the garden which features carpet grass and manicured hedges. The hotel houses a gym and an outdoor pool.
        Airport shuttle, city shuttle, conferencing facilities, babysitting and laundry services are provided at an additional charge.
        The main building is fitted with CCTV cameras and the premises are guarded by security personnel.
        Thika Town and Kenol Petrol Station are close to Golden Palm Breeze Hotel. </string>
    <string name="golden_palm_breeze_addr">Golden Palm Breeze Hotel Kenol, Kenol-Muranga Road, Sanduku La Posta 30, MURANGA</string>

    <string name="mukurwe_name">Mukurwe Wa Nyagathanga</string>
    <string name="mukurwe_desc">Said to be the cradle of the Agikuyu   people, the fabled Mukurwe wa Nyagathanga is situated in Gaturi location in Kiharu Constituency.
        History has it that mythical garden was focal point of dispersal of the Agikuyu after setting their foot in the slopes of Mount Kenya.
        At the site, Kikuyu Traditional elders often perform rituals, and the Kikuyu elite use it to bring the community together for a  cause  of common interest.
        Mukurwe wa Nyagathanga  is  gazetted  National monument  under  the charge of  National Museums of Kenya and Muranga County government.
        The  historical  site has  ten huts  named  after the ten Gikuyu clans.</string>
    <string name="mukurwe_addr">Mukurwe Wa Nyagathanga AGIKUYU Cultural Center</string>
    <string name="aberdare_range_name">Aberdare National Park</string>
    <string name="aberdare_range_desc">Encircled by the wild and beautiful moorlands of the third highest mountain range in Kenya,
        Aberdare National Park offers a mist-wreathed realm where rhinos roam through lichen-hung forests,
        spectacular waterfalls plunge into churning pools, and trout-ﬁlled streams cascade through mossy dells.</string>
    <string name="aberdare_range_addr">Aberdare National Park</string>

    <string name="muranga_high_sch_name">Murang’a High School</string>
    <string name="muranga_high_sch_desc">Murang’a High School is a Public Secondary School, located in Located in Murang’a Town near Murang’a Town, Kiharu Constituency in Murang’a County</string>
    <string name="muranga_high_sch_addr">MURANGA HIGH SCHOOL</string>
    <string name="muranga_uni_name">Murang’a University of Technology</string>
    <string name="muranga_uni_desc">Murang’a University of Technology is the Successor of Murang’a University College, a former constituent College of Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology after being elevated from Murang’a College of Technology</string>
    <string name="muranga_uni_addr">Murang’a University of Technology, Murang’a University College, Muranga, MURANGA TOWN (fomer Fort Hall)</string>

    <string name="east_end_mall_name">East End Mall</string>
    <string name="east_end_mall_desc">East End Mall is a modern commercial property Situated at Kangari Township,Murang`a County along Kangari- Githumu- Thika Road.
        Ideal for: Hospitals. colleges/university campus, medical centre, NGO’s.
</string>
    <string name="east_end_mall_addr">kangari township muranga county</string>
</resources>
